Guide to the Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Alumni Files, 1876-
Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Alumni Files, 1876-
- Series II. 1900-1999
  - 1990-1999
    - Galvis, Pilar, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 92)
    - Glick, Lauren S., 1992 (Box 26, Folder 93)
    - Gold, Richard C., 1992 (Box 26, Folder 94)
    - Graham, Mary E., 1992 (Box 26, Folder 95)
    - Greenberger, Leah J., 1992 (Box 26, Folder 96)
    - Hazel, Alison M., 1992 (Box 26, Folder 97)
    - Heinzerling, Heidi M., 1992 (Box 26, Folder 98)
    - Hillman, Jeanne M., 1992 (Box 26, Folder 99)
    - Hunter, Linda S., 1992 (Box 26, Folder 100)
    - Kantrowitz, Lawrence B., 1992 (Box 26, Folder 101)
    - Kearing, Jocelyn A., 1992 (Box 26, Folder 102)
    - Kelly, Michael P., 1992 (Box 26, Folder 103)
    - Kleps, Nora A., 1992 (Box 26, Folder 104)
    - Klohnen, Andreas, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Kornreich, Bruce G., 1992 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Leverenz, Nancy E., 1992 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Licari, Louis G., 1992 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Malloy, Kelly A. [Farrell, Kelly M.], 1992 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Marsico, Lisa A., 1992 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - McKenna, Antigone M., 1992 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Monachelli, Margaret T., 1992 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Morrisey, James K., 1992 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Mostoller, Margaret, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Muffoletto, Bonnie L., 1992 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Nezezon, Joel M., 1992 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Nowak, Mark S., 1992 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Peck, Penny M., 1992 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Pini, Maria T., 1992 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Polehinke, Thomas A., 1992 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Posner, Lysa P., 1992 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Purcell, Karen A., 1992 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Radinsky, MaryAnn G., 1992 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Ramos, Lillian, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Reid, Richard W., 1992 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Rodgers, Robinson R., 1992 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Saunders, Katherine D. [Hodgson, Katherine D.], 1992 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Schottman, Kate, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Silbiger, Mark H., 1992 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Spaulding, Barry W., Jr., 1992 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Stummer, Margaret R., 1992 (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Sullivan, Thomas C., 1992 (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - Surman, Vivien, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Tapley, Kathleen, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - Trachtenberg, David K., 1992 (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - Triana, Maria S., 1992 (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - Vannerson, Lesley A., 1992 (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - Waldow, Dorraine, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - Weston, Haley S., 1992 (Box 27, Folder 35)
    - Willimann, Reinemarie T., 1992 (Box 27, Folder 36)
    - Wilson, Christine S., 1992 (Box 27, Folder 37)
    - Wohl, Deborah D., 1992 (Box 27, Folder 38)
    - Altschul, Martina, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 39)
    - Bartlett, Steven M., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 40)
    - Bergendorff, Kim, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 41)
    - Berger, Allan L., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 42)
    - Beyer, Michael J., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 43)
    - Boehringer, Michelle, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 44)
    - Brush, Michelle, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 45)
    - Bryant, Nelva J., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 46)
    - Butler, Emily Caldwell, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 47)
    - Cella, Janine M., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 48)
    - Childers, Pamela J., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 49)
    - Cobb, Matthew A., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 50)
    - Collier, Karyn L., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 51)
    - Cote, Etienne, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 52)
    - Cronin, Carin P., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 53)
    - DeLorenzo, Kenneth, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 54)
    - Diggle, Edmund A., III, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 55)
    - Eirmann, Laura Ann, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 56)
    - Famigletti, Nancy E., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 57)
    - Fleckinstein, Polly Arnold, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 58)
    - Fornes, Mary Lee, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 59)
    - Fournier, Jeanne C., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 60)
    - Freedman, William K., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 61)
    - Gantt, Kenneth, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 62)
    - Gosson, Gloria L., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 63)
    - Gurshman, Rebecca, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 64)
    - Heller, Ruth L., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 65)
    - Herzog, Maria, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 66)
    - Hoffman, Dwight J., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 67)
    - Hornig, Linda S., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 68)
    - Howlett, Brian A., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 69)
    - Jamrosz, Gregory Francis, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 70)
    - Joseph, Sara A., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 71)
    - Karp, Beth, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 72)
    - Kearns, Karen S., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 73)
    - Kim, Carol A., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 74)
    - Knezevich, Mary, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 75)
    - Kreis, Cathy A., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 76)
    - Labreque, Kimberly I. L. [Lettis, Kimberly], 1993 (Box 27, Folder 77)
    - LaPoint, Jeffrey, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 78)
    - Leister, Mary, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 79)
    - Lormore, Michael J., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 80)
    - Man Warren, Trenna L., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 81)
    - Marrero, Marisol, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 82)
    - Marschman, Kristin A., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 83)
    - McNamara, Paul S., Jr., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 84)
    - Mignemi, Donna, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 85)
    - Moks, Pamela A., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 86)
    - Ofsie, Susan, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 87)
    - O'Leary, Lisa A., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 88)
    - Pagliaro, Michael S., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 89)
    - Plotkin, Michael O., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 90)
    - Puerto, David A., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 91)
    - Rassnick, Kenneth M., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 92)
    - Reiss, Adam, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 93)
    - Richards, Amy, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 94)
    - Robinson, Timothy M., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 95)
    - Rocchio, Christopher J., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 96)
    - Roellke, Kim G., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 97)
    - Romano, Virginia S., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 98)
    - Rubinstein, Jennie, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 99)
    - Rummel, David P., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 100)
    - Santisi, David S., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 101)
    - Sarna, Carolyn, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 102)
    - Schanbacher, Barbara, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 103)
    - Schunk, Kristina L., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 104)
    - Scrivani, Peter Vincent, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 105)
    - Seagren, Mary Ann, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 106)
    - Sikora, Nancy K., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 107)
    - Smith, Miranda, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 108)
    - Thode, Barbara, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 109)
    - Valdes, Richard, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 110)
    - Vrba, Janine, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 111)
    - Waddell, Lori, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 112)
    - Wells-Eisenhaure, Hannah [Wells, Hannah], 1993 (Box 27, Folder 113)
    - Wilson, Georgette D., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 114)
    - Wratten, Wayne D., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 115)
    - Young, Sandra E., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 116)
    - Zelinski, Karen, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 117)
    - Adelsohn, Deborah S., 1994 (Box 27, Folder 118)
    - Arasu, Prema, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 119)
    - Arrington, Edward L., Jr., 1994 (Box 27, Folder 120)
    - Appel, Leslie, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 121)
    - Balacich, Michele M., 1994 (Box 27, Folder 122)
    - Barry, Amanda M., 1994 (Box 27, Folder 123)
    - Bertoldo, Jon P., 1994 (Box 27, Folder 124)
    - Bowers, Jeremy G., 1994 (Box 27, Folder 125)
    - Brown, Cynthia A., 1994 (Box 27, Folder 126)
    - Brown, Thomas J., 1994 (Box 27, Folder 127)
    - Buchholz, Lawrence, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 128)
    - Carpenter, Kelli, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 129)
    - Cho, Jane O., 1994 (Box 27, Folder 130)
    - Cockburn, Tregel M., 1994 (Box 27, Folder 131)
    - Collins, Brian, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 132)
    - Corcoran, Pamela A., 1994 (Box 27, Folder 133)
    - Cromie, Bonny Rob, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 134)
    - Daly, Holly A., 1994 (Box 27, Folder 135)
    - Das, Helena Himani, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 136)
    - Dattner, Michael, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 137)
    - Davies-Brown, Fiona, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 138)
    - DiGiovanni, Maria E., 1994 (Box 27, Folder 139)
    - Donovan, Jeanette L., 1994 (Box 27, Folder 140)
    - Fagraeus, Charlotte, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 141)
    - Fernandez, Luis R., 1994 (Box 27, Folder 142)
    - Fischman, Suzanne, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 143)
    - Flores, Anthony, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 144)
    - Focacci, Mark, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 145)
    - Freiman, Shlomo, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 146)
    - Friedhofer, Ann, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 147)
    - Gardner, Jennifer, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 148)
    - Goggin, Justin M., 1994 (Box 27, Folder 149)
    - Goldman, Elizabeth, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 150)
    - Goodman, Leah K., 1994 (Box 27, Folder 151)
    - Griffin, Mary Jean, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 152)
    - Hanchett, Lori A., 1994 (Box 27, Folder 253)
    - Hulse, Michelle P., 1994 (Box 27, Folder 154)
    - Impellizeri, Joseph A., 1994 (Box 27, Folder 155)
    - Jarvis, Emily, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 156)
    - Jones, L. Katherine [Miller, Katherine Jones], 1994 (Box 27, Folder 157)
    - Kelly, Khayya, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 58)
    - Koren-Roth, Yossi, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 159)
    - Lee, David E., 1994 (Box 27, Folder 160)
    - LeLeonnec, Marc, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 161)
    - Lewis, Jane, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 162)
    - Lucia, Patricia Anne, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 163)
    - Maldonado, Cristina P., 1994 (Box 27, Folder 164)
    - McArthur-Wicks, Deborah, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 165)
    - McAvoy, Sandra J., 1994 (Box 27, Folder 166)
    - Millard, Jo Ann, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 167)
    - Moslock, Brenda L., 1994 (Box 27, Folder 168)
    - Moyle, Robin B., 1994 (Box 27, Folder 169)
    - Nichols, Elizabeth S., 1994 (Box 27, Folder 170)
    - Northrup, Nicole C., 1994 (Box 27, Folder 171)
    - Pacy, John M., 1994 (Box 27, Folder 172)
    - Padilla, Anthony W., 1994 (Box 27, Folder 173)
    - Petrillo, Suzanne M., 1994 (Box 27, Folder 174)
    - Pizano, Sara, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 175)
    - Pugh, Nancy, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 176)
    - Rath, Amy K., 1994 (Box 27, Folder 177)
    - Reimann, Justie Lee, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 178)
    - Richter, Julie Ann, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 179)
      1967-2006
    - Riskin, Gregory S., 1994 (Box 27, Folder 180)
    - Schoenborn, William C., 1994 (Box 27, Folder 181)
    - Schwartz, Beth, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 182)
    - Schwartz, Debra E., 1994 (Box 27, Folder 183)
    - Shaw, Nancy, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 184)
    - Smith, Charla D., 1994 (Box 27, Folder 185)
    - Smith, Julia Margaret, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 186)
    - Solomon, Robin Kerri, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 187)
    - Sparks, Jennifer R., 1994 (Box 27, Folder 188)
    - Sponseller, Brett A., 1994 (Box 27, Folder 189)
    - Thall, Emily E., 1994 (Box 27, Folder 190)
    - Tighe, Ellyn Kae, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 191)
    - Tobin, Regina L., 1994 (Box 27, Folder 192)
    - Tully, Lauren, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 193)
    - Walcott, Jeffrey, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 194)
    - Wicinski, Joseph Michael, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 195)
    - Willsey, Amy, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 196)
    - Zabella, Ari S., 1994 (Box 27, Folder 197)
    - Zane, Suzanne, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 198)
    - Adin, Christopher, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 199)
    - Argersinger, Michelle, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 200)
    - Bartol, Jacqueline, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 201)
    - Bliss, Stuart, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 202)
    - Bliss, Susan K. [Keller, Susan K.], 1996 (Box 27, Folder 203)
    - Boshart, Christine, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 204)
    - Boyer, Jennifer, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 205)
    - Breickner, Liesl, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 206)
    - Brittain-Adin, Darcy B. [Adin, Darcy B.], 1996 (Box 27, Folder 207)
    - Brockett, Leisa M., 1996 (Box 27, Folder 208)
    - Catinchi, Katherine, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 209)
    - Congel, Kathleen, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 210)
    - Cummings, Kevin, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 211)
    - Curran, Nancy, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 212)
    - Daly, Mary K. [McClaine, Mary K.], 1996 (Box 27, Folder 213)
    - Daut, Elizabeth, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 214)
    - DiGrazia, Mara, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 215)
    - Donnelly, Alice Marie, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 216)
    - Doria-Rose, Vincent Paul, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 217)
    - Duffield, Laurie, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 218)
    - Fallon, Luke, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 219)
    - Farrell, Cynthia, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 220)
    - Feldman, Mindy, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 221)
    - Ferber, Michael, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 222)
    - Fessler, Karen, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 223)
    - Fischer, Teresa A., 1996 (Box 27, Folder 224)
    - Flowers, John, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 225)
    - Fondacaro, John, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 226)
    - Ford, Sarah, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 227)
    - Fosgate, Geoffrey, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 228)
    - Fredericks, Russell, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 229)
    - Fusco, Jason, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 230)
    - Geraughty, Michael, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 231)
    - Gilligan, Rachel, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 232)
    - Gioseffi, Margaret, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 233)
    - Greer, Deanna, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 234)
    - Johnson, Joann, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 235)
    - Kablack, Kerry, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 236)
    - Kimmel, Susan, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 237)
    - Kochis, Stephen, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 238)
    - Krakowiak, Jill, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 239)
    - Kraus, Elisabeth, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 240)
    - Lander, Jennifer, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 241)
    - Love, Karen, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 242)
    - Makolinski, Kathleen, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Maurer, Jennifer, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Meyer, Alyce, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Moody, Karyn, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Moore, Catherine, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Neeson, Jeanne, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - O'Neal, Robin, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Pembleton-Corbett, Julie, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Perry, Noelle, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Praul, Darryl, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Reynolds, Ashley, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Robbins, Keith, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Roosevelt, Jessica, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Ruffing, Nancy, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Schuldt, Lora, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Scott, Robert, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Smith, Kelly, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Stelling, Dawn, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Stockett, Glen, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Treglia, Linda, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Vamvakias, Peter, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Wachtman, Lynn M., 1996 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Wakefield, Crystal, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Weis, Ransome, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Werkhoven, Carole, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Westerdahl, Maura, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Williams, Megan, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - Wingate, Lisa, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - Wolfson, Suzanne, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - Zachos, Terri, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - Zambelli, Alicia, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - Adamo, Eileen, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 32)
    - Alaimo, Joseph F., 1997 (Box 28, Folder 33)
    - Antkowiak, Matthew, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 34)
    - Arns, Jacquelyn, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 35)
    - Bardsley, Judith, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 36)
    - Barone, Georgina, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 37)
    - Black, Brian, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 38)
    - Braun, Maria, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 39)
    - Budner, Michelle, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 40)
    - Canady, Lauren, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 41)
    - Chapman, Nancy J., 1997 (Box 28, Folder 42)
    - Cherry, Scott, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 43)
    - De Groff, Leslie Scott, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 44)
    - Diehl, Christina, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 45)
    - Di Filippo, Franca, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 46)
    - Donis, Katherine N., 1997 (Box 28, Folder 47)
    - Dressler, Demian, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 48)
    - Erickson, Patricia, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 49)
    - Feldman, Katherine, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 50)
    - Fisher, Carolyn, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 51)
    - Gevanthor, Jeffrey, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 52)
    - Goldmann, Michael, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 53)
    - Gorra, Michael Ferris, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 54)
    - Grinnell, Patricia Ernst, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 55)
    - Hegarty, Catherine, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 56)
    - Heilman, Nathan, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 57)
    - Hunt, Melanie, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 58)
    - Isroe, Leslie, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 59)
    - Jones, Denise [Ross, Denise R.] [Martin, Denise R.], 1997 (Box 28, Folder 60)
    - Kattman, Kelly, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 61)
    - Korich, Jodi Angela, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 62)
    - Kull, Patricia, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 63)
    - Lagana, Maria, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 64)
    - Le Bars, Elsa, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 65)
    - Lee, Justine, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 66)
    - Linnetz, Eric, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 67)
    - MacInnis, Emily, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 68)
    - Matthies, Erika, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 69)
    - Misner, Tracy, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 70)
      Class photo; Received Cornell DVM degree?
    - Morin, Jennifer R., 1997 (Box 28, Folder 71)
    - Moews, Julie, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 72)
    - Motta, Fernando, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 73)
    - Murphy, Elizabeth, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 74)
    - Nydam, Daryl, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 75)
    - Oberlander, Robin, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 76)
    - Odre, Suzanne, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 77)
    - Parker, Vikki, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 78)
    - Peterson, Lisa, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 79)
    - Pomerantz, Julie, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 80)
    - Rabuffo, Tara Susan, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 81)
    - Ravina, Gabrielle, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 82)
    - Rudick, Kelly, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 83)
    - Ryan, Patricia M., 1997 (Box 28, Folder 84)
    - Schulman, Jacqueline, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 85)
    - Schultz, Kimberly, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 86)
    - Schreiber, Karen, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 87)
    - Schwartz, Beth, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 88)
    - Shah, Reena, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 89)
    - Skoglund, Todd, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 90)
    - Stephens, Julie, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 91)
    - Spencer, Melanie, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 92)
    - Steinberg, Lisa, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 93)
    - Stiner, Catherine, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 94)
    - Sternefeld, Gayle Elizabeth, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 95)
    - Stonefield, Jay, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 96)
    - Stronger, Rebecca, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 97)
    - Sutor, Scott, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 98)
    - Tarasoff, Sandra, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 99)
    - Tello, Ce'sar, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 100)
    - Thomas, Mark J., 1997 (Box 28, Folder 101)
    - Uhler, Brenton D., 1997 (Box 28, Folder 102)
    - Vygantas, Kristina, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 103)
    - Wade, Laura, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 104)
    - Wajda, Melissa, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 105)
    - Wallace, Kevin, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 106)
    - Zinna, Patricia, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 107)
    - Alberti, Michael Holzhauser [Holzhauser-Alberti, Michael], 1998 (Box 28, Folder 108)
    - Allegrezza, Thomas A., 1998 (Box 28, Folder 109)
    - Allen, Nancy, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 110)
    - Anderson, Lenore Menger, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 111)
    - Balkman, Cheryl, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 112)
    - Barrientos, Alexandra, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 113)
    - Bashore, Cynthia Jennings, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 114)
    - Bentley, Adrienne, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 115)
    - Berntson, Julia F., 1998 (Box 28, Folder 116)
    - Bloom, Bridget A., 1998 (Box 28, Folder 117)
    - Brofman, Peter, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 118)
    - Byron, Christopher, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 119)
    - Ceglowski, C.J., 1998 (Box 28, Folder 120)
    - Chadam, Maria T., 1998 (Box 28, Folder 121)
    - Chan, Daniel L., 1998 (Box 28, Folder 122)
    - Collins, Jennifer, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 123)
    - Consigli, Joseph A., 1998 (Box 28, Folder 124)
    - Corey, Pamela, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 125)
    - Corrigan, Erin, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 126)
    - Davis, Garrett, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 127)
    - DeHart, Malissa A., 1998 (Box 28, Folder 128)
    - Delia, Laura L., 1998 (Box 28, Folder 129)
    - DeMeo, Jennifer, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 130)
    - Dunn, Michael, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 131)
    - Edmunds, Elizabeth E., 1998 (Box 28, Folder 132)
    - Ettinger, Susan, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 133)
    - Farrelly, John, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 134)
    - Fish, Jeffrey, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 135)
    - Fixman, Julie, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 136)
    - Fleury, Tasha, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 137)
    - Foley, Robert, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 138)
    - Fox, Colleen, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 139)
    - Foy, John S., 1998 (Box 28, Folder 140)
    - Gannon, Kerry, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 141)
    - Godlewski, Brenda, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 142)
    - Golub, Stacey, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 143)
    - Gross, Shelley Ruth, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 144)
    - Gurtman, Marc, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 145)
    - Higgins, Jacqueline R., 1998 (Box 28, Folder 146)
    - Hubbard, Susan Patricia, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 147)
    - Klein, Susan C., 1998 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Koenig, Ross, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Kumar, Gita, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Laidley, Karen P., 1998 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Levey, Rachel, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Levy, Fred Robert, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Kindo, Claire, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - MacGregor, John M., 1998 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Martinez,Victoria, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Morbelli, Laetitia, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Negrin, Karen, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Nevill, Heather, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Nolte, Dawn M., 1998 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - O'Loughlin, Carrie, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Olson, Victoria M., 1998 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Pershing, Emily, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Petersen, Christine A., 1998 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Piwonka, Margaret Catharine, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Pixton, Morna, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Pollock, Glen, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Protos, Polly, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Putnam, Laurie, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Quinn, Sara A., 1998 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Ralphs, Chris, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Rawlinson, Jennifer E., 1998 (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - Reed, Christine, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Sachs, Amy Claire, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - Sanders, Sara Yarnall, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - Sanfilippo, Mary Ann, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - Smith, Rachel L., 1998 (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - Smith-Vallone, Theodora J., 1998 (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - Stone, Deborah C., 1998 (Box 29, Folder 32)
    - Szulczewski, Olivia, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 33)
    - Van Noy, Jennifer Lynn Berger, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 34)
    - Virkler, Paul D., 1998 (Box 29, Folder 35)
    - Wakshlag, Joseph J., 1998 (Box 29, Folder 36)
    - Wells, Annette, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 37)
    - Wiley, Krista M., 1998 (Box 29, Folder 38)
    - Winter, Matthew, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 39)
    - Wu, Sandra Suleen, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 40)
    - Xanthos, Mary, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 41)
    - Baker, Lynn M., 1999 (Box 29, Folder 42)
    - Bancroft, Lisa R., 1999 (Box 29, Folder 43)
    - Bayer, Virginia E., 1999 (Box 29, Folder 44)
    - Boyadjian, Suzan, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 45)
    - Bradshaw, Lori L., 1999 (Box 29, Folder 46)
    - Brandes, Deirdre E., 1999 (Box 29, Folder 47)
    - Breckenridge, Wendy M., 1999 (Box 29, Folder 48)
    - Cangeleri, Chris P., 1999 (Box 29, Folder 49)
    - Childs, Sara E., 1999 (Box 29, Folder 50)
    - Christensen, Eric R., 1999 (Box 29, Folder 51)
    - Cohen, Michele, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 52)
    - Danboise, Heather L., 1999 (Box 29, Folder 53)
    - Davis, Kechia M., 1999 (Box 29, Folder 54)
    - Deibel, Christiane R. "Nina", 1999 (Box 29, Folder 55)
    - Del Borgo, Anne K., 1999 (Box 29, Folder 56)
    - DeMoy, Karen P., 1999 (Box 29, Folder 57)
    - Egli, Michelle D., 1999 (Box 29, Folder 58)
    - Fahy, Clare T., 1999 (Box 29, Folder 59)
    - Falcone, Megan Nalevanko, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 60)
    - Feiler, Celia E. [Shafer, Celia E.], 1999 (Box 29, Folder 61)
    - Good, Lillian I., 1999 (Box 29, Folder 62)
    - Graziano, Jennifer Paige R. [Pongratz, Jennifer Paige] [Adams, Jennifer Paige], 1999 (Box 29, Folder 63)
    - Grosse, Ariana G., 1999 (Box 29, Folder 64)
    - Hartman, Wendy J., 1999 (Box 29, Folder 65)
    - Hess, Jennifer, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 66)
    - Hinsley, Sarina, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 67)